quris.com 2003-06-21

# Quris, Inc. :: About Us

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

Quris is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We collect information from our site visitors at several different points on our web site. 

**Requesting Information**  
In order to request more information from Quris, including white papers, research reports, information about upcoming events or to have a Quris representative contact them, a visitor must first complete a “request for contact” form. This form requires the user to give contact information, such as name, job title, company name, street address, phone number and email address. We use this information to contact the user about services for which he or she has expressed interest. 

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes logging Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track a visitor’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Email Communication from Quris**  
If a visitor wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. We use that information to fulfill a visitor’s request for information and to personalize the newsletter. 

Out of respect for our visitor’s privacy we provide a clear way to opt out of these communications. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter may opt out of receiving these communications by replying to the message and providing the word “unsubscribe” in the subject line. We also offer a clickthrough opt-out mechanism in every email we deliver. 

In our newsletters, we may include a tracking image in all of our rich text and HTML-formatted email messages. This tracking image is activated when the message is opened, if the recipient of the message is connected to the Internet. The tracking image records the time and date that the individual recipient opened the message, and potentially flags the email address of the recipient as one that is capable of receiving HTML-based email messages. This capability helps us send email to recipients in a format they can read, allows us to track the aggregate number of emails opened, and to determine whether an individual recipient has opened the message. If the recipient is offline or cannot receive rich text or HTML-formatted email, the recipient will not receive a functioning tracking image. 

Additionally, in our newsletters, we may code links in email messages with tracking identifiers. These identifiers record the time and date that the individual recipient clicked on a specific link. This capability allows us to track the aggregate number of messages clicked, the aggregate number of clicks on an individual link, and to determine whether an individual recipient has clicked on an individual link. 

**Resume Submissions**  
A visitor may email their resume to Quris. The visitor is required to provide their name and email address along with a resume. The information is used to screen candidates and contact them for interviews.. A third party contractor may review resumes for screening purposes. 

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Quris, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

We use email links throughout the site to allow visitors to contact us directly with questions or comments. We use the information collected to respond directly to questions and comments, and will file those comments in order to improve the site and our services. 

**Sharing**  
We will not share, barter or sell visitor information to third parties, except in the cases outlined below. 

First, though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. 

Second, in the event Quris goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, visitors’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. 

**Changes to this Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so our visitors are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

* * *

**Our Work with Our Clients**  
Quris is the integrated email agency designed to help Fortune 1000 businesses realize the value of the email channel through strategic planning, creative product development, data analysis and high-performance technology solutions. 

Our role in supporting our clients may include: 

  * Hosting of customer profile data
  * Message creation and personalization
  * Message delivery
  * Reporting on and analysis of data
  * Delivery of email program results information back to our clients

The importance of all personally identifiable information associated with our clients and their customers is of utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of information, utilizing encryption software. We store the information in a secure environment in a Class A Internet Service Provider. 

In our work with clients, we may include a tracking image in all of our rich text and HTML-formatted email messages. This tracking image is activated when the message is opened, if the recipient of the message is connected to the Internet. The tracking image records the time and date that the individual recipient opened the message, and potentially flags the email address of the recipient as one that is capable of receiving HTML-based email messages. This capability helps us send email to recipients in a format they can read, allows us to track the aggregate number of emails opened, and to determine whether an individual recipient has opened the message. If the recipient is offline or cannot receive rich text or HTML-formatted email, the recipient will not receive a functioning tracking image. 

Additionally, in our work with clients, we may code links in email messages with tracking identifiers. These identifiers record the time and date that the individual recipient clicked on a specific link. This capability allows us to track the aggregate number of messages clicked, the aggregate number of clicks on an individual link, and to determine whether an individual recipient has clicked on an individual link. 

Quris is contractually bound to keep our clients' customer data private and this data is never shared across clients.
